(DRIFTY MUSIC BEGINS)
- [ROBOT] STATE OF EMERGENCY.
(DRIFTY MUSIC CONTINUES)
♪ YEAH, YEAH ♪
♪ REMEMBER THE TIME, BABY ♪
♪ I AIN'T GOT NO MONEY ♪
♪ I AIN'T GOT NO CAR
TO TAKE YOU ON A DATE ♪
♪ I CAN'T EVEN BUY YOU FLOWERS ♪
♪ BUT TOGETHER WE COULD
BE THE PERFECT SOULMATES ♪
♪ TALK TO ME GIRL ♪
♪ OH, BABY, IT'S ALRIGHT NOW,
YOU AIN'T GOTTA FLAUNT FOR ME ♪
♪ IF WE GO AND TOUCH, YOU CAN
STILL TOUCH MY LOVE, IT'S FREE ♪
♪ WE CAN WORK WITHOUT THE
PERKS JUST YOU AND ME ♪
♪ WORK IT OUT 'TIL
WE GET IT RIGHT ♪
♪ BABY IF YOU STRIP,
YOU CAN GET A TIP ♪
♪ 'CAUSE I LIKE YOU
JUST THE WAY YOU ARE ♪
♪ I'M ABOUT TO STRIP
AND I'M WELL EQUIPPED ♪
♪ CAN YOU HANDLE
ME THE WAY I'M ON ♪
♪ I DON'T NEED THE
G'S OR THE CAR KEYS ♪
♪ BOY I LIKE YOU JUST
THE WAY YOU ARE ♪
♪ LET ME SEE YA STRIP,
YOU CAN GET A TIP ♪
♪ 'CAUSE I LIKE,
I LIKE, I LIKE ♪
♪ I AIN'T GOT NO VISA ♪
♪ I AIN'T GOT NO RED
AMERICAN EXPRESS ♪
♪ WE CAN'T GO NOWHERE EXOTIC ♪
♪ IT DON'T MATTER 'CAUSE I'M
THE ONE THAT LOVES YOU BEST ♪
♪ TALK TO ME GIRL ♪
♪ OH, BABY, IT'S ALRIGHT NOW,
YOU AIN'T GOTTA FLAUNT FOR ME ♪
♪ IF WE GO AND TOUCH, YOU CAN
STILL TOUCH MY LOVE, IT'S FREE ♪
♪ WE CAN WORK WITHOUT THE
PERKS JUST YOU AND ME ♪
♪ WORK IT OUT 'TIL
WE GET IT RIGHT ♪
♪ BABY IF YOU STRIP,
YOU CAN GET A TIP ♪
♪ 'CAUSE I LIKE YOU
JUST THE WAY YOU ARE ♪
♪ I'M ABOUT TO STRIP
AND I'M WELL EQUIPPED ♪
♪ CAN YOU HANDLE
ME THE WAY I'M ON ♪
♪ I DON'T NEED THE
G'S OR THE CAR KEYS ♪
♪ BOY I LIKE YOU JUST
THE WAY YOU ARE ♪
♪ LET ME SEE YA STRIP,
YOU CAN GET A TIP ♪
♪ 'CAUSE I LIKE YOU
JUST THE WAY YOU ARE ♪
♪ BABY GIRL, I DON'T
GOT A HUGE OL' HOUSE ♪
♪ I RENT A ROOM IN A HOUSE ♪
♪ LISTEN BABY GIRL, I
AIN'T GOT A MOTORBOAT ♪
♪ BUT I CAN FLOAT YA BOAT ♪
♪ SO LISTEN BABY GIRL ♪
♪ ONCE YOU GET A DOSE OF
D.O.E. YOU GON' WANT SOME MO' ♪
♪ SO LISTEN BABY GIRL ♪
♪ WHEN I MAKE IT I WANT YOU
THERE, WANT YOU THERE, YEAH ♪
♪ YEAH MY MONEY AIN'T
ALOOF LIKE PHIL AND THEM ♪
♪ AND IT'S REALLY NOT
QUITE LOW AS LSN ♪
♪ YOUR BODY AIN'T
PAMELA ANDERSON ♪
♪ IT'S A STRUGGLE JUST TO
GET YOU IN THE CARAVAN ♪
♪ BUT LISTEN BABY GIRL ♪
♪ BEFORE I LET YOU LOSE A
POUND, I'LL BUY A BIGGER CAR ♪
♪ SO LISTEN BABY GIRL ♪
♪ I LOVE YOU JUST THE WAY
YOU ARE, THE WAY YOU ARE ♪
♪ OH, BABY, IT'S ALL RIGHT ♪
♪ NOW YOU AIN'T
GOTTA FLAUNT FOR ME ♪
♪ IF WE GO DUTCH, YOU CAN STILL
TOUCH MY LOVE, IT'S FREE ♪
♪ WE CAN WORK WITHOUT THE
PERKS, JUST YOU AND ME ♪
♪ THUG IT OUT 'TIL
WE GET IT RIGHT ♪
♪ BABY, IF YOU STRIP,
YOU CAN GET A TIP ♪
♪ 'CAUSE I LIKE YOU
JUST THE WAY YOU ARE ♪
♪ I'M ABOUT TO STRIP
AND I'M WELL EQUIPPED ♪
♪ CAN YOU HANDLE
ME THE WAY I'M ON ♪
♪ I DON'T NEED THE
G'S OR THE CAR KEYS ♪
♪ BOY, I LIKE YOU
JUST THE WAY YOU ARE ♪
♪ LET ME SEE YA STRIP,
YOU CAN GET A TIP ♪
♪ 'CAUSE I LIKE YOU
JUST THE WAY YOU ARE ♪
♪ BABY, IF YOU STRIP,
YOU CAN GET A TIP ♪
♪ 'CAUSE I LIKE YOU
JUST THE WAY YOU ARE ♪
♪ I'M ABOUT TO STRIP
AND I'M WELL EQUIPPED ♪
♪ CAN YOU HANDLE
ME THE WAY I'M ON ♪
♪ I DON'T NEED THE
G'S OR THE CAR KEYS ♪
♪ BOY, I LIKE YOU
JUST THE WAY YOU ARE ♪
♪ LET ME SEE YA STRIP,
YOU CAN GET A TIP ♪
♪ 'CAUSE I LIKE,
I LIKE, I LIKE ♪